<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HC Swimsite</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HC Swimsite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Join</title>
      <link>/club/club-how-to-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-how-to-join/</guid>
      <description>To join the club, you make contact with the collegiate pool
How to Join HC Swim Club Memberships &amp;amp; Swimming Season Club membership is annual (1 Oct – 30 Sep) and is aligned with Swimming Tasmania (STAS) registration. This means that there is one annual registration/renewal process which includes both the Club and STAS membership. Club membership and STAS membership are compulsory for all squad members as this ensures that both the Club and swimmers are insured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HC Swim Club</title>
      <link>/people/people-hc-swim-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-hc-swim-club/</guid>
      <description>Postal Address HC Swim Club Inc.
PO Box 109
Sandy Bay, TAS 7006
Bank Transfers The following details are provided in the event members need to make Bank Transfers to the club. These are for HC Swim Club payments only (e.g for purchase of Uniform or payment for entry to Club Event).
Acct Name: Hutchins Collegiate Swim Club Inc.
BSB: 017 010 ACCT: 1093 27269
Always put your Surname and an Item Summary in the transfer description.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-target-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-target-squad/</guid>
      <description>Squad description The Target Squad provides coaching and support for swimmers who are very committed to training and competing at the highest levels of competition. Swimmers will continue to develop all aspects of stroke technique, fitness and race skills with a focus on race strategy as they prepare for their competitions.
This squad caters for swimmers who are eligible to compete at high levels of competition such as Victorian Age/Open Championships and Australian Age/Open Championships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/club/club-code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 01:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Swimming Tasmania Policies As a minimum, all HC Swim Club Members should be aware of (and review) Swimming Tasmania&amp;rsquo;s policies with regard to:
 Code of Conduct Member Welfare Child Welfare  You can access copies of these policies here.
Member Protection Information Officers (MPIO) - Head Coach, Members of the Committee
Conduct of swimmers and parents It is expected that swimmers will display a high standard of behavior when associated with the Club - training, swim meets and social functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimming Tas SC Regional Champs, Hobart</title>
      <link>/events/events-swimming-tas-sc-regional-champs-hobart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 04:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/events-swimming-tas-sc-regional-champs-hobart/</guid>
      <description>SESSION 1 - Warm up is from 8am with the first event from 8.30am. SESSION 2 - Warm up is from 3pm with the first event from 3.30pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maddi Palser</title>
      <link>/people/people-maddi-palser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-maddi-palser/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior State Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-senior-state-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-senior-state-squad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Club Structure</title>
      <link>/club/club-club-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-club-structure/</guid>
      <description>The HC Swim Club is an Incorporated Association, governed by the Associations Incorporations Act 1964 and associated regulations.
The Club is managed by a committee of volunteers.
The Principals of St. Michael&amp;rsquo;s Collegiate School and the Hutchins School are patrons of the Club.
HC Swim Club is an affiliate member of Swimming Tasmania, our governing body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swimming Tas SC Regional Champs, Launceston</title>
      <link>/events/events-swimming-tas-sc-regional-champs-launceston/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 04:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/events-swimming-tas-sc-regional-champs-launceston/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collegiate Pool</title>
      <link>/people/people-collegiate-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-collegiate-pool/</guid>
      <description>The Collegiate Pool is a 25m, six-lane, heated indoor pool located on the corner of Molle &amp;amp; Davey Street in the city of Hobart.
The Collegiate Pool is open to the public and offers a safe, clean and friendly environment to swim.
Entry to the Collegiate Pool is via the School entrance on the corner of Molle &amp;amp; Macquarie Streets.
We are open seven days a week and offer:
 Learn to Swim Lap Swimming Fitness Squad training options  Our professional teachers provided quality service and are passionate about assisting individual&amp;rsquo;s to improve their health, fitness and life skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-state-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-state-squad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HC Swim Club Tags</title>
      <link>/club/club-hc-swim-club-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 06:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-hc-swim-club-tags/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The HC Swim Club provides a skills level structure which effectively starts where the Learn to Swim levels finish and takes swimmers up to Elite level.
Each level (Aquatic 9 to 14) require swimmers to obtain and demonstrate effective and consistent application of specific skills (stroke and racing) supporting their own development as a swimmer. All swimmers will be assesses on scheduled Assessment Days (or Tag Sessions) based on the required for each of the levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Swimming Tas SC Championships</title>
      <link>/events/events-2019-swimming-tas-sc-championships/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 04:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/events-2019-swimming-tas-sc-championships/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-development-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-development-squad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-junior-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-junior-squad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kylie Jones</title>
      <link>/people/people-kylie-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-kylie-jones/</guid>
      <description>The place would fall apart without her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Annual Celebration Dinner</title>
      <link>/events/events-2019-annual-celebration-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 02:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/events-2019-annual-celebration-dinner/</guid>
      <description>The HC Swim Club warmly invites all members and their families to the 2019 Annual Celebration Dinner. Its a great family night to celebrate the success of our swimmers ans thank out coaches, parents and supporterd with lots of fun and great lucky door prizes!
Where: Royal Yacht Club of Tasmania, Sandy Bay.
Time: 6.30pm
Cost: Adults $30 per head, Kids $20
Book here. Book before 20 April 2019 and go in the draw to win 2 Gold Class Movie Passes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Racers Squad</title>
      <link>/squads/squads-junior-racers-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/squads/squads-junior-racers-squad/</guid>
      <description>Squad description The Junior Racers Squad is the natural progression from Learn to Swim lessons. Swimmers learn training/racing skills which they practice at club meets and Swimming Tasmania Qualifying Trials
Junior Racers train for 42 weeks per year.
Costs Club membership (includes Swimming Tasmania registration) 6 – 8 years old $105 9 years old - $160
Coaching fee (includes Pool Pass) - $90 per month
Required equipment  Goggles (plus a spare pair in your swim bag Club cap (plus a spare cap in your swim bag) Drink bottle Mesh swimming bag Kickboard Flippers  Training sessions White Tag squad members are encouraged to attend 2 -3 training sessions a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Brennemo</title>
      <link>/people/people-rachel-brennemo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-rachel-brennemo/</guid>
      <description>Rachel Rickards (ASCTA Silver License) is the Head Coach. She has 20 years experience in coaching swimmers at the top level. Awarded the 2012 Tasmanian Coach of the Year, she coached the 2012-13 Tasmanian Swimmer of the Year and Tasmaninan Open Water Swimmer of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane Pederson</title>
      <link>/people/people-jane-pederson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-jane-pederson/</guid>
      <description>The place would fall apart without her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adam Briggs</title>
      <link>/people/people-adam-briggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-adam-briggs/</guid>
      <description>Adam Briggs has been involved with the HC Swim Club for 14 years, from a swimmer through to completing his Junior License Course. Whilst at HC, Adam has been mentored and coached through his swimming by Rachel Rickards and Harry Kink who have helped develop the skills to take on Junior Squad training back in 2009. Previous to this, Adam had also served as club captain for 2 years working with younger swimmers at swim meets and at training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bianca Moore</title>
      <link>/people/people-bianca-moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-bianca-moore/</guid>
      <description>Making champions of the Junior Racers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Kink</title>
      <link>/people/people-harry-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/people-harry-kink/</guid>
      <description>The funniest coach</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>