<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clubs on HC Swimsite</title>
    <link>/club/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clubs on HC Swimsite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Join</title>
      <link>/club/club-how-to-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-how-to-join/</guid>
      <description>To join the club, you make contact with the collegiate pool
How to Join HC Swim Club Memberships &amp;amp; Swimming Season Club membership is annual (1 Oct – 30 Sep) and is aligned with Swimming Tasmania (STAS) registration. This means that there is one annual registration/renewal process which includes both the Club and STAS membership. Club membership and STAS membership are compulsory for all squad members as this ensures that both the Club and swimmers are insured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/club/club-code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 01:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Swimming Tasmania Policies As a minimum, all HC Swim Club Members should be aware of (and review) Swimming Tasmania&amp;rsquo;s policies with regard to:
 Code of Conduct Member Welfare Child Welfare  You can access copies of these policies here.
Member Protection Information Officers (MPIO) - Head Coach, Members of the Committee
Conduct of swimmers and parents It is expected that swimmers will display a high standard of behavior when associated with the Club - training, swim meets and social functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Club Structure</title>
      <link>/club/club-club-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-club-structure/</guid>
      <description>The HC Swim Club is an Incorporated Association, governed by the Associations Incorporations Act 1964 and associated regulations.
The Club is managed by a committee of volunteers.
The Principals of St. Michael&amp;rsquo;s Collegiate School and the Hutchins School are patrons of the Club.
HC Swim Club is an affiliate member of Swimming Tasmania, our governing body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HC Swim Club Tags</title>
      <link>/club/club-hc-swim-club-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 06:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-hc-swim-club-tags/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The HC Swim Club provides a skills level structure which effectively starts where the Learn to Swim levels finish and takes swimmers up to Elite level.
Each level (Aquatic 9 to 14) require swimmers to obtain and demonstrate effective and consistent application of specific skills (stroke and racing) supporting their own development as a swimmer. All swimmers will be assesses on scheduled Assessment Days (or Tag Sessions) based on the required for each of the levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleanliness</title>
      <link>/club/club-cleanliness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 08:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/club/club-cleanliness/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to dry your toes</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>